Guide to the Richard Marshall Collection of Gay Erotica and Pornography MSS.498
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VIII. Web Fiction, 1986-2003, undated; 7 Linear Feet in 7 record cartons.; 3 electronic discs (cd-rom)
  - Butt Feast, Marc, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 98)
  - Butt Sniffer (Part 3), Marc, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 99)
  - The Call, Copper, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 100)
  - Camping Dad's (Part 2), Roderick Shafton, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 101)
  - Camping with Uncle Bob, Get2it, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 102)
  - Car Wash Man, Nick, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 103)
  - Card Slave Buddies, Unknown, Undated (Box 20, Folder 104)
  - Careful What You Say In Jest!, Bbrunner4, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 105)
  - Carlito's Table (Parts 1, 2), Raunchiboi69, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 106)
  - Carpe Diem, Jon Logan, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 107)
  - Caught by Dad, Daddy's Boy, Undated (Box 20, Folder 108)
  - Caught In A Rundown (Parts 1, 2), PeterAinLA, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 109)
  - The Cave (Part 1), Rimpigfl, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 110)
  - Cell Sex, Dwolf5, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 111)
  - Chance Encounter, Champ, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 112)
  - Cheating Lover, Bawdy Pen, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 113)
  - City Slave, Scatwoman, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 114)
  - Cleanin' Up Daddy, Jerry & Eric, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 115)
  - The Climbing Hut, aled7, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 116)
  - Coach, Chris Newman, Undated (Box 20, Folder 117)
  - Coach, Matti, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 118)
  - Coach: A Gay Chainletter, MuscleBear, exPECtation, Unknown, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 119)
  - Coach Madison, Daniel Townsend, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 120)
  - Coach's Ass, Part 2, CDBOY, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 121)
  - Cody, Scott Brenson, Undated (Box 20, Folder 122)
  - College Boys During Spring Break, ScatStud, Undated (Box 20, Folder 123)
  - Construction Dad (Parts 1, 2), Russell, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 124)
  - Construction Hole, RC Barber, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 125)
  - Construction Ride Home, JD, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 126)
  - Construction Site Daddies; Afternoon Shower with Cousin Zack; In Bed with My Uncle; Caught By Uncle, Ruff Tuff UK; Mark K; Mark, Undated (Box 20, Folder 127)
  - Construction Stud Foreman (Part 2), Jay Cee, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 128)
  - The Construction Stud Foreman (Parts 1,2 4-6), Jay Cee, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 129)
  - The Construction Worker's Son (Parts 2,3), Rimpigfl, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 130)
  - The Convention, Manekel, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 131)
  - Convention of a Lifetime, Cliff Simpson, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 132)
  - Cop, Greg Griggs, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Cop, Ripinstick, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Cop, Unknown, Undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Cop (Part 2), Unknown, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Cop Cadet, Bill Drake, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Cop Encounter, Unknown, Undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Cop Sex, Sam Rad, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Copsucker, Uknown author, and Copsucker (Part II), Dick Hunter, 1998, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Cottage Fantasy, Antoms, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Country Boy, Marc Tremaine, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Country Life, an143969, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Countrylife, Kevin Mackenzie, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Cowboy, Scott Benson, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - A Cowboy Story, Unknown, Undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Cruising For Piss (Parts 1,2), Ron Kelly, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Cum Contest, An22313, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Cum Slut, Cum Drinker, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Cumshots & Pisstreams: Confessions of a Teenage Toilet (Parts 1-3), Jay, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Cuntboy (Part 1), Maipenraikhap, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - A Cup of Joe, Backlash, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Curiosity (Chapters 1-3,6-7,1-15,19,20-22), Shaver Boy, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Custodial Help, David L. Hass, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - A Dad and His Boy: A Love Story, PIGBoy32, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Dad and Me First Pee, Fckmedad, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Dad and Me in the Cornfield, R.N.E., Undated (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Dad and Me on the Farm, Duu634, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Dad and the Coach, Joshua A. Laff, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Dad-Discovers-Me, Alexander Phaeton, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Dad Fucked him at the ADB, coolblue35, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Dad in the Shower (Parts 1-3), Thom, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Dad, Me and our Horse Farm, Victorianboy, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Dad Teaches Me, duu634, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Daddies in the Lockers, Man Loving, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Daddy Daddy (Part 6), CandyMan, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Daddy Punishes His Boys With Sex, kinky_uncut_daddy, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Daddy Stan (Part 1), Frank Ward, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Daddy's Cocksucker, PigBoy32, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Daddy's Good Little Boy, Rimpigfl, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Daddy's Home, Dade Bryant, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Daddy's Pickups (parts 1, 2), Roderick Shafton, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Dad's Buddy Rene, Nick, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Dad's Club (Part 2), Maipenraikhap, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Dad's Cock, Ron, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Dad's Cockslave, raman5436, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Dad's Condom, Dkscorpio, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Dad's Demonstation, Edward Bangor, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Dad's Dirty Little Boy (Part 1 - 3), RimPigfl, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Dad's Golden Boy (Parts 1, 2), RimPigfl, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Dad's Lust, RC, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Dad's Outhouse, Mark Thomas, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Dad's Piss Fag (Part 1-5), Unknown, Undated (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Dad's Piss Fag 1, 4, and 5, Unknown, Undated (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Dad's Pussy, Happenstance, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Dad's Randy 4 (Chapter 12-15), Tyler Thane, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Dad's Shit Slave (Part 1), Josh Carr, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Dad's Stink, Marc, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Dad's "Woodie", Balsam8, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Danny's School Humiliation, Maipenraikhap, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - The Dare!, T. Bears, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - Dario 'n Dad (Part 2), D. B. Reed, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Dark Corners, Loopy, Undated (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Darn Hot, Pete Conway, Undated (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Dave's Bitch, Jay S, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - A Day at the Beach, Unknown, Undated (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - A Day in July, Paul and Don, Undated (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Denver, the Biker, Roderick Shafton, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - Depraved (Parts1- 3), Bawdy Pen, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Depraved Cravings, Toilet Mike, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Destroyed Mind, Devil Dog, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - Deviant Lust, 12 Inch Jesus, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - Diaper, Unknown, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - Directions (Part 1), Pete, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - Dirty Boy Next Door, AmuseBouche, Undated (Box 21, Folder 73)
  - Dirty Little Altar Boys, Roderick Shafton, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - Dirtpig: A Weekend of Raunch, Unknown, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - Dog Pound Daze, (Parts 4-6, 11), lennoxbear, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - Dog Surprise, Varstin, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 77)
  - Dominated By Doug (Parts 4, 11-13), Perryxyz, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 78)
  - Domination of a Quarterback-04, Jonathan, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 79)
  - Doorbell, Anthony Thomas, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 80)
  - The Doting Wife, Roderick Shafton, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 81)
  - Doug Does The Gang 10, Chartoe, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 82)
  - Douglasville Dilemma, Sniff42, Undated (Box 21, Folder 83)
  - Doug's Experience, Paul Haakonsen, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 84)
  - Down on the Docks, Roderick Shafton, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 85)
  - Downstairs At The Fox... (Part 1-3), Willingmike, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 86)
  - Drew Gets Passed Around (Part 1), Brandon Richardson, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 87)
  - Drill Sergeant Gets Drilled (Parts 1, 2), Bill Drake, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 88)
  - Drunk Enough, Roderick Shafton, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 89)
  - The Dumping Ground, Scatboy, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 90)
  - Eatin' It At The Baths (Parts 1, 2), Bkcycler, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 91)
  - Eating Latino Dump: A True Story, RimGuy, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 92)
  - Eating Nevada Beef, Rimguy, Undated (Box 21, Folder 93)
  - Eating Shit In Dr. Jack's Lab; A Night To Remember; Fly Catcher, Butch, Toilet Mike; Sxuldev8, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 94)
  - Engineered, V9irjim, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 95)
  - The English Boy 24: 'Peter's Story', Philip Burbidge, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 96)
  - Enslaved, Dale10, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 97)
  - Enslaved Followup, Maipenraikhap, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 98)
  - Eric, Hidden 12, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 99)
  - An Evening with Gamal, Arablover, Undated (Box 21, Folder 100)
  - The Executive, Eryck, Undated (Box 21, Folder 101)
  - An Experiment with Manuel, loopy, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 102)
  - Family Business (Parts 5-6, 8-11), Jack Doegh, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Family Friction (Part 5), Rim4you, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Family Fuck (Parts 1-13), Roarr201, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Fantasy Fulfilled at the Watersports Club, Wellington Club, Undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Fanta$y $eduction, Hair Lover, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Farmer Brown, Nathan Harvey, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Father, Unknown, Undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Father Takes Charge Pt. 3, Phill, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Father's Night (Parts 1-3), LCdrObrien, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - The Favor, Bawdypen, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - The Favor, Bbrunner4, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Feeding and Breeding Sean & Brendan (Part 2), Dick Hunter, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - A Few Good Men (Parts 2, 3), Billy Bob, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Field Manuvers, R. Keith Peck, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Finally, Used As The Slut I Am, Isuckall, Undated (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - First Time With Dad, Unknown, Undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Five the Hard Way, Wildstyle, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - The Flange, Bushy Pits, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Flycatcher, Sxuldev8, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Foggy Night, Tjo1, Undated (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Folsom Street, Wolter, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Football Fuck, F.U.C.K, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Forced Dog Fuck, Beef Rian, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Force Fucked in the Forest, Rectufill, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Foreman, Myoder, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Forest Rain, Rene, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Fourth of July Faggot, and Fourth of July Too, Maipenraikhap, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Frank's Boys **Friday Night** (Part 1), Unknown, Undated (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Frat Basement (Part 5), RimPigfl, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Frat Boy Master, S C, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Frathouse Visitor (Parts 1, 2), Roderick Shafton, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Fucked By a Pro, Bill Drake, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Fucked Up (Parts 1-3,6,7), Roarr201, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Fuckin Around With Brother and Dad (Part 1), Anthony Jamieson, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Furface Fantasy, Galen, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Gang Bang, donaldelliot11, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Gang Banging Mario Lopez #3, Vraxis, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Garage Buddies, Mike, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - The Gardner (Part 5A, 5B), Twinkie The Kid, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Gaston's Toilet, loopy, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - General DIscharge, Happenstance, Undated (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Get A Grip: Hunter Men 02, Marc Tremaine, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Getting It From The Big Boys Fantasy Stud Fucking (Parts 1-3), Joe Webster, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Gimmie A Ride, Cowboy, Rimpigfl, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Gio, Hapenstance, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Glory Hole Dangers, spike4me, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Glory Hole Employment (Part 1, 2), Goo Gobbler, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Glory Queen 21: The Hunting Trip, Grtbttm2, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Glory, Sparta, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Gloryhole (Chapter 1), Unknown, Undated (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Gloryhole III, Unknown, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Go West Young Man 5, Nicholas Romanov, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Gone Fishin', R. Keith Peck, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Gotta Have It (Parts 1, 2), Rim4You, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - The Greece Monkey (Part 1), Shaggy, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - The Green Light (Part 1), Joe Peters, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Gringo, Nathan Harvey, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - The Groundskeeper, Warren Piece, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Gym Fuck, Unknown, Undated (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Gym Routine, Piano Guy, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Gym Slave, Al if you like it, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Hairy Four Fuck, Jackson Smith, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - Hairy Wonder, David L. Hass, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - Hakim and His Dad-3, Aaron Hernan, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - Halstead: Welcome, Twenty Bucks, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - Handy Man Special, an143969, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - Hard Hat Area: This is a Watersports Story, Tom, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - Harder, Ram Me Harder; The Adventures of Dan'te & Uncle Bud, Jim Deerboy; A. Gordon Dan'te, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - Hardon Family 03: Park Patrol & Hardon Family 05: Convention Surprise, Marc Tremaine, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - Hardon High 03: Head Coach, Tremaine, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 70)
  - Have a Look at Manlover, Unknown, Undated (Box 22, Folder 71)
  - Have Balls Will Travel, Twenty Bucks, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 72)
  - The Hazing (Parts 8-9, 12-13), maipenraikhap, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 73)
  - The Head Chef (Part 2), Twinkie The Kid, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 74)
  - A Hell of a Price to Pay, Diesel Sniffer, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 75)
  - Hellbent-for-Leatherneck; Jarhead Stud; Camp Wad; Pig for Cock; PFC Check-In; Devil Dog Pupps, Devil Dog; CLayBoY, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 76)
  - Here Comes the Son, Unknown, Undated (Box 22, Folder 77)
  - Highgate Prison, Alex J, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 78)
  - Highway Patrol (Part 1), An143969, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 79)
  - Hippie Boy Raunch, BobZuma, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 80)
  - Hiram, Roderick Shafton, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 81)
  - His Pimp, Roderick Shafton, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 82)
  - Holding Cell, Bawdy Pen, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 83)
  - Honeyboy, Eric Smith, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 84)
  - Horny Guy Tails #1, Eat Me!, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 85)
  - Horny Guy Tails From Minnesota, An106131, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 86)
  - Horny Guy Tails from Minnesota (#13), Unknown, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 87)
  - Horny Truckers, Christian, Undated (Box 22, Folder 88)
  - Horse Diary (Part 2), Paulo Richart, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 89)
  - Hot Daddy, Agr13yoTop, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 90)
  - Hot Daddy, Harry, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 91)
  - Hot for Uncle Jeff (Part 9), Rim4you, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 92)
  - Hot For Uncle Jeff (Parts 14-16), Rim4You, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 93)
  - Hot Jock, Unknown, Undated (Box 22, Folder 94)
  - Hot Jocks (Parts 1-3), Flt2, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 95)
  - Hot Shower, Bear Hunter, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 96)
  - Hotel Construction Workers, Rri610, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 97)
  - The House of Hell (Part 5), Phill, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 98)
  - House of Incest (Part 3), Unknown, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 99)
  - How I Became a Closet Queer (Chapters 1, 2), U4orcedme, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 100)
  - How I Became A Queer, Vincenzo, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 101)
  - The Hunter (Part 1), Joe Law, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 102)
  - The Hunter Men 01: Take That! General Motors, Marc Tremaine, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 103)
  - The Hunting Lodge, Edward08, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 104)
  - Hypno-Therapist, maipenraikhap, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 105)
  - I Can't Get Enough of Mom's Boyfriend, Kevin East Bay, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - I Dream of Man-Pussy; Campus Cruise, Man Lover, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - I Learn to Take It (Chapters 1-10), Joe Law, 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - I Learn to Take It (Chapters 11-16, 18-26), Joe Law, 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - I Sucked My Father's Cock, Local Boy, Undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - I Want You To Fuck Me, Vivek Kumar, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - I was Manolo's Toilet; Bobby was the Boss (Parts 1, 2), Arablover, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - I was Manolo's Toilet, Arablover; Joe, Tony, and Ted, Micfriend; Nick and Danny, Loopy; Open Up, Unknown, Undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - I'm A Slut for Daddy Dick, Unknown, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - In the Dark, Jamie Anderson, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Indecent Arrangement, Phoenixfr, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Irrigating Alabama, Jason Roberts, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - The Italian and the Spade, Edward Bangor, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Italian Dad - Part II, MosseyCJ, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - The Itch, and The Itch (part IV), Glaucon55, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 15-16)
  - The J Tape, Jake Enright, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Jack and Me, Botpuppy, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Jack the Jock, Scathole, Undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Jack Wants to Feed, Big Jack, Undated (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Jackin' Off My Dad When He Was Drunk & Asleep, capataur, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Jake's Study Hall, Glaucon55, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Jared Feeds, Slick, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Jarhead Perversion, Devil Dog, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Jarhead Stud, Devil Dog, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Jason and the Cop, Jason P, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Jerker's Weekend Out (Parts 1-4), Phill, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Jim and His Uncle, Andy Anderson, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Jock Fever, Marc, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Jock Sex Slave (Parts 2-4), perseus, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Jocksucker (Chapter 2), John Clark, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Joe, Tony and Ted, Micfriend, Undated (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Joey's Awakening: New Life (Parts 1,7,9,10,19,20), Joe Webster, 2000-2002 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Jogger Feeds On My 9 (Parts 1, 2), Muslickstud4u, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - John and My Dad, CoolBlue35, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Johnny, Joni, and Chad, Maipenraikhap, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Johnny's Boi; My Thanksgiving Dinner; A Night to Remember, Loopy; PIG; Toilet Mike, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Jose, the Puerto Rican Shitter, Rich Dick, Undated (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Josh's Story, agrk3yotop, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Journal of a Pervert, Bawdypen, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - The Journey (Part 3, 5, 6), Rim4You, 1996-2000 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - The Judge's Disposition, Roderick Shafton, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Just for Fun, Joe Law, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Keith, Manager, Adult Books, David L. Hass, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Kelly's Toilet, loopy, Undated (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - The Kid Bastards In Bunkhouse 40 (Chapter 5), Jeff Kincaid, Undated (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Kidnap!, A1 Writer, Undated (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Kip's Letter (Number 3-5, 8), Kip Ketter, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Kips Letter: The Last Letter, Maipenraikhap, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Laborer's Apprentice, Manny, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Latin Lover, Spa, David L. Hass, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Latin Lust, Up Arrow, Undated (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - The Latrine, Leather Man, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Latrine Duty, Rim4you, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - LeaDR House (Chapter 6-7), Theo North, Undated (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Leather Master, Rimpigfl, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Liberty (Parts 5,8,9), Doug Gage, Undated (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Lifestyles BBS: Connecticut's Premier Hot Spot, Beardlover, Undated (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Like Father Like Son, Moist Dreams, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Like Father, Like Sons (Parts 1-3), RC61Austin, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - Little Boys At Old Charlie's Place, Xwriter, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - A Little R&R, Rim4You, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - The Little Stud, RimPig, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - Live for Today, Devil Dog, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 64)
  - The Load Master, Wizzo, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 65)
  - Locker Room, Matti, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 66)
  - Locker Room Fun, Unknown, Undated (Box 23, Folder 67)
  - Locker Room Meeting, Juergn Eichemueller, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 68)
  - Locker Room Shower Stud, Phineas Narco, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 69)
  - Lockerroom Shower Studs, Unknown, Undated (Box 23, Folder 70)
  - Lockeroom Stink (Parts 1,3,5) Rim4You, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 71)
  - The Logger, Da Copper, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 72)
  - Loggerfuck, Furr, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 73)
  - Look At That Dickhead! (Cont.), 3u7d8, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 74)
  - Lost In Lust, Devil Dog, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 75)
  - Lovers, Nathan Harvey, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 76)
  - Lovers Dad, Bill Drake, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 77)
  - The Lubejob, An147051, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 78)
  - The Lucky Charm (Parts 1-4), Little Bad, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 79)
  - M2M Archive, man2man, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 80)
  - Mac Stevens and the Ten Loads (Parts 1-3), Cooper Smith, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 81)
  - Mac Stevens BBQ (Parts 1-3), Cooper Smith, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 82)
  - Mac Stevens: While the Cat's Away (Parts 1-3), Cooper Smith, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 83)
  - Mac's Frustrating Day (Part 2), PoliceFan36,1999; Mac's Frustrating Night, PoliceFan36 (Box 23, Folder 84)
  - The Mailman Delivers, Chadd Lusst, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 85)
  - The Maintenance Man and the Tearoom, Furr, Undated (Box 23, Folder 86)
  - Making A Man of Me; Cleanin' Up Daddy, Mikeyeddie; Sandiego, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 87)
  - Making a Man of Me; Party Boy, Mike, EK, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 88)
  - Making Deliveries (Book 4- Part 1), Slick, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 89)
  - Making Deliveries, Slick, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 90)
  - Making of a Shit-Eater, Romacub, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 91)
  - Malt Liquor Drinker, K. Meacy, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 92)
  - The Man Down the Hall, Roderick Shafton, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 93)
  - Manolo Returns, Arablover, Undated (Box 23, Folder 94)
  - Marine Capture, bushypits, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 95)
  - Marine Latrine (Part 1), Marc, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 96)
  - Marine Playtime, h_daze, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 97)
  - Marine Training (Parts 1 - 3), Etienne, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 98)
  - A Marine's Fantasy, Devil Dog, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 99)
  - A Marine's Slave Training - Part 1: Rebellion, Biker, Undated (Box 23, Folder 100)
  - A Marine's Story (Part 2), Rimpigfl, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 101)
  - Mark's Uncle (Part 1), Unknown, Undated (Box 23, Folder 102)
  - Matt Snaps His Fingers, loopy, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 103)
  - Max Stevens and Sgt Straight (Part 6), Cooper, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 104)
  - Me, Dad and Jacob (Parts 1, 2), Fleetwood, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 105)
  - Men At Work, Unknown, Undated (Box 23, Folder 106)
  - Menage A Todd, PlowBoyOH, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 107)
  - The Men's Room (Parts 1-3), Rim4you, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 108)
  - The Michael Tapes (Parts 1-4), Marc Tremaine, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Mid-South Mess, Scott Baker, Undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Midnight In the Garden of Lust, Joe Wilson, Undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Midwest Raunch, An129138, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Miguel, noone, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Mike Gets His Boy, Black Flag, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Mike - Story of a Marine, Rimpigfl, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Military Dad, IncstBoy, Undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Military Madness (Parts 1-3), Bawdy Pen, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - The Milk Bar (Parts 1-7, 13), white collar, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Milking Cowboy, Rim4you, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - The Milkman (Parts 1-3), Glaucon55, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - More Family Fun; Family Fun-Forever, Balsam8, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - The Most Disturbing Behavior, loopy, Undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Motel (Parts 1-6), Joe Law, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Mountain Men (Part 3), Roderick Shafton, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Mountain Men (Muscle Bear), Myoder, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 17)